<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>monitoring on CloudOdyssey</title>
		<link>https://diabhey.github.io/tags/monitoring/</link>
		<description>Recent content in monitoring </description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		
  		<language>en</language>
		
		<managingEditor>Page(/tags/monitoring) (Abhimanyu Selvan)</managingEditor>
    	
  		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
		<atom:link href="/tags/monitoring/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>Multi-node K8s at home</title>
			<link>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/04/18/2021-04-18-local-k8s/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/04/18/2021-04-18-local-k8s/</guid>
			<description>Nowadays, there are many off-the-shelf solutions to get k8s up and running. Here are some of the Lightweight Kubernetes out there,
 kind microk8s k3s LKE (not free)  These k8s distribution have ample documentation and examples online that will easily help you set it up.
Let&amp;rsquo;s do it the hard way In this blog post, I will guide the readers through a series of steps that I did to set up a multi-node K8s cluster at home.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Remote Server Monitoring and Observability</title>
			<link>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/04/12/2021-04-12-remote-server-monitoring/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/04/12/2021-04-12-remote-server-monitoring/</guid>
			<description>The stations will be deployed across the globe and we need a way to effectively monitor and alert us in real-time. Thanks to Prometheus, all the heavy-lifting is done for us. In this post, I will run through a series of steps that is required to setup Prometheus on a Linux server and then go ahead and setup Grafana Cloud as our observability platform through which can intuitively gain insights from our data sources across the globe.</description>
		</item>
      	
		<item>
			<title>Cloudception</title>
			<link>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/02/14/2021-02-14-cloudception/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid>https://diabhey.github.io/2021/02/14/2021-02-14-cloudception/</guid>
			<description>On Valentines day, I decided to go public about my love affair with the cloud. The more time I spend in the open source world, the stronger I feel to share my thoughts with all the CloudSurfers out there.
I intend to use this space as a digital journal for all things cloud-native. The posts will be centered around the following topics but certainly not limited to
  Cloud native tools and software</description>
		</item>
      	
	</channel>
</rss>
